{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818832251","data":{"timestamp":" 947818832251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 2e1aabec-c6fa-48de-81ec-e02fbcf447f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mdo_mka-mdo-nde"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818849888","data":{"timestamp":" 947818849888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818865425","data":{"timestamp":" 947818865425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818866786","data":{"timestamp":" 947818866785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818870080","data":{"timestamp":" 947818870080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818880065","data":{"timestamp":" 947818880065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818881353","data":{"timestamp":" 947818881353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818900310","data":{"timestamp":" 947818900310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818911475","data":{"timestamp":" 947818911475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818918043","data":{"timestamp":" 947818918043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818939001","data":{"timestamp":" 947818939001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818950865","data":{"timestamp":" 947818950865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818958134","data":{"timestamp":" 947818958134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818962012","data":{"timestamp":" 947818962012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" e5438b1c-24a0-4761-925c-bfe20af4829d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818971067","data":{"timestamp":" 947818971067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 0ed7fc58-01bc-4eef-a850-2e0091be0afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818971294","data":{"timestamp":" 947818971294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 0ed7fc58-01bc-4eef-a850-2e0091be0afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818972026","data":{"timestamp":" 947818972026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 0ed7fc58-01bc-4eef-a850-2e0091be0afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818972129","data":{"timestamp":" 947818972128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 0ed7fc58-01bc-4eef-a850-2e0091be0afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818983992","data":{"timestamp":" 947818983992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 55789f34-0c48-43a0-9292-91b513590173"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bwa_ngi-bwa-tha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947818990937","data":{"timestamp":" 947818990937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 55789f34-0c48-43a0-9292-91b513590173"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mdo_mka-mdo-nde"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mdo"," userResponse":" mdo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819014639","data":{"timestamp":" 947819014639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 55789f34-0c48-43a0-9292-91b513590173"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_sho-mko-mfa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819017724","data":{"timestamp":" 947819017724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_055941"," gameId":" 55789f34-0c48-43a0-9292-91b513590173"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_sho-mko-mfa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}